<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="title_changelog" translatable="false">Changelog</string>

    <string name="changelog" translatable="false"><b>1.6.0</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>Thanks to the support of awesome community members, this app is now not only localized in English and German, but also Spanish, French, Italian and Norwegian (Bokmål). Thanks so much for your help! 🙏🙏🙏</li>
        \n<li>Small under-the-hood updates to make the app even more reliable.</li>
        \n
        \n<b>1.5.1</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>Fixes a bug where the rates wouldn\'t update, when exchangerate.host is used.</li>
        \n<li>Library updates to improve stability and performance.</li>
        \n
        \n<b>1.5.0</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>Select between two API providers: <b>exchangerate.host</b> and <b>frankfurter.app</b></li>
        \n<li>You can now support the developer by donating with PayPal. Find the link in the settings. (F-Droid version only.)</li>
        \n<li>More UI improvements</li>
        \n
        \n<b>1.4.1</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>UI improvements</li>
        \n
        \n<b>1.4.0</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>It is now possible to manually refresh the rates. Check it out in the overflow menu.</li>
        \n<li>Performance improvements</li>
        \n
        \n<b>1.3.0</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li><b>So many more currencies! Over 160 in total, now!!</b> That\'s because Currencies switched to a different API. The old one (exchangeratesapi.io) changed to a subscription model without any prior warning. NOT GOOD! Our new provider will be exchangerate.host.</li>
        \n<li>That also means, that the last couple of days, the exchange rates couldn\'t be refreshed. That\'s fixed now, of course.</li>
        \n<li>Also, the refresh process itself got improved, so at least next time something like that happens, you\'ll get a notice.</li>
        \n<li>Small UI improvements</li>
        \n
        \n<b>1.2.0</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li><b>17 new currencies!</b> That\'s now 50 in total. 🥳 Too many to name them all. However, a lot of popular vacation destinations in the middle east and the caribbean are now included: UAE, Qatar, Barbados, Bahamas, Cuba, …</li>
        \n<li>To stay on top of all those new choices, a <b>search</b> is now available in the currency picker.</li>
        \n<li>The picker now also shows a currency\'s <b>full name</b>, not only its code. An awesome addition, in combination with the search. Try it out!</li>
        \n
        \n<b>1.1.1</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>Minor improvements (typo \'n stuff)</li>
        \n
        \n<b>1.1.0</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>Depending on your credit card agreement, your bank may charge a fee on all foreign exchange transactions.\nYou can now include that fee in the calculations, so you know how much you really pay. 🙂</li>
        \n
        \n<b>1.0.1</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>Fix possible crash on Android 11</li>
        \n
        \n<b>1.0.0</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>Added German translation 🇩🇪</li>
        \n<li>Minor improvement: App size decreased by 50%!</li>
        \n<li>App seems pretty stable: Public 1.0 release! 🥳🥳🥳</li>
        \n
        \n<b>0.2.2</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>Minor improvements</li>
        \n
        \n<b>0.2.1</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>Better error handling</li>
        \n<li>Minor improvements</li>
        \n
        \n<b>0.2.0</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>Added a copy function: Long click on the value you want to copy</li>
        \n
        \n<b>0.1.0</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>More fail-proof updating of the currency rates</li>
        \n<li>Added a disclaimer</li>
        \n<li>Added this changelog</li>
        \n
        \n<b>0.0.1</b>
        \n⸻
        \n<li>Initial pre-release</li>
    </string>

</resources>
